Hello friends, how are you all? Welcome to
our YouTube channel Stock Market
Point. Friends, today we are going to talk again
about ICICI Lombard. As you may be seeing here,
in today's trading session we have
seen a negative side closing with 4%
and along with this, friends, its
delivery report has
given us a clear positive signal here because
according to its delivery report, the delivery
quantity is
around 2295218, which you may be seeing here
and today's total trade
quantity is around 3700000,
whose delivery percentage is around 60%
and friends, if
I compare this delivery report with the delivery report of the previous trading station, then
in that condition, it is much higher than my 5 training sessions.
Friends, as you may be seeing here, so
if we believe this delivery report, then
we may see a positive opening here in the coming trading session. So along with this,
friends, we have to  There is a need to be a little cautious
because of its two
support areas, that is, the first support area was
1226 and the second support area was
around 1218, so both the levels have
broken out on the negative side
and we have also seen closing on the negative side. We will
talk further about its
support and resistance levels,
but before talking about those levels, a
little information about this YouTube channel will be given to all of you in the
form of support for all the income generated from this YouTube channel,
friends, so
please give your love and support to this YouTube channel and along with this,
friends, the first earning of this YouTube channel
is almost complete
and where to use it, please
tell us in the comment box below, do watch the video completely
and if you have visited this YouTube channel for the
first time, then please like the
video and subscribe to the channel
and all the credit for this work
goes to all of you friends, as you must be seeing here,
we have
seen the closing of today's trading session around 1210,
which is the current condition we have  According to this, the
support area is
around Rs.1200, so
if we see a negative opening in the coming trading session, then the
first negative movement can be from 1200 to
around
12195 and if both the
levels break out simultaneously on the negative side, then
we can also see the possibility of decline around 1190 to around 1187. Let me
talk about the movement on the positive side, friends,
if we see a positive opening of the side from 1210 here,
then the first positive
movement can be around 1212 to around 12-18
rupees and if it
successfully breaks out of the challenge, then the
possibility of positive movement can increase here and
we can also see it around 1221 to 1226.
Along with this, friends, if we talk about
its fast positive or negative side
movement here, then
if we look at the vanishing time frame here,
friends, until the range is
not seen breaking out of 1240  It comes and
until we see this range acting as a support level,
we see very little possibility of fast positive movement here, so
friends, if the closing gives itself a
downside from 1207 in any condition,
then after that we need to be a little cautious here
because after the level of ₹1200
breaks out on the negative side,
the chances of decline may increase, so
friends, if you liked the video, then please
like the video, subscribe to the channel and
turn on the notification bell so that
you keep getting such videos related to the market, along with this, friends, thank you very much from the bottom of your heart for
giving your valuable time for this video,
Jai Hind.